<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>hazm &#8211; SASSO</title>
	<atom:link href="./index.html" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<description>Authentic Italian Flavours</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 09:38:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>./../../../wp-content/uploads/2021/07/favicon.png</url>
	<title>hazm &#8211; SASSO</title>
	<link>./../../../index.html</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Savour the Essence of Italy with Sasso&#8217;s Tiramisu</title>
		<link>./../../../savour-the-essence-of-italy-with-sassos-tiramisu/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Antonie Cruz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 09:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Pizza]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[al waab]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doha]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fine dining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[golden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hazm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[italian fine dining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[italian restaurant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[luxury]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pizza]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[truffle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[west walk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1278</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Savour the Essence of Italy with Sasso&#8217;s Tiramisu At Sasso, we&#8217;re thrilled to introduce our latest culinary masterpiece, the classic Italian dessert &#8211; Tiramisu. This delectable creation embodies the very essence of Italy, capturing the rich and authentic flavours that have made Tiramisu a beloved dessert worldwide. A Taste of Italy Sasso&#8217;s Tiramisu is a [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Savour the Essence of Italy with Sasso&#8217;s Tiramisu</strong></p>



<p>At Sasso, we&#8217;re thrilled to introduce our latest culinary masterpiece, the classic Italian dessert &#8211; Tiramisu. This delectable creation embodies the very essence of Italy, capturing the rich and authentic flavours that have made Tiramisu a beloved dessert worldwide.</p>



<p><strong>A Taste of Italy</strong></p>



<p>Sasso&#8217;s Tiramisu is a tribute to the traditions and flavours of Italy. Every bite transports you to the streets of Rome or the cafes of Florence, as you experience the perfect blend of creamy mascarpone, the richness of espresso-soaked ladyfingers, and the delicate dusting of cocoa.</p>



<p><strong>A New Addition</strong></p>



<p>We&#8217;re delighted to add this exquisite Tiramisu to our menu, expanding the array of authentic Italian offerings at Sasso. Whether you&#8217;re craving a sweet finale to your meal or simply seeking a taste of Italy, our Tiramisu is the perfect choice.</p>



<p><strong>The Perfect Dessert</strong></p>



<p>Tiramisu is more than a dessert; it&#8217;s an experience. It&#8217;s the sweet note that concludes an Italian feast on a high, and it&#8217;s the indulgence that brightens your day. Sharing it with loved ones or savoring it alone, Sasso&#8217;s Tiramisu is your passport to an Italian culinary journey.</p>



<p><strong>Available Now</strong></p>



<p>Ready to savor the essence of Italy at Sasso? Our Tiramisu is available now, and it&#8217;s waiting for you to experience the true taste of Italy. Join us for a slice of Italy&#8217;s culinary heritage – Sasso&#8217;s Tiramisu, a classic dessert that transcends borders.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The first-ever Golden Truffle Pizza in Doha</title>
		<link>./../../../golden-truffle-pizza/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Antonie Cruz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 13:18:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Pizza]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[al waab]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doha]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fine dining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[golden]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hazm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[italian fine dining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[italian restaurant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[luxury]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pizza]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[truffle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[west walk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1263</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We pride ourselves on following traditional Italian cuisine; whilst adding our&#160;luxurious touch. Elevate your dining experience with our latest addition to the menu &#8211; the Golden Truffle Pizza. It&#8217;s an Italian masterpiece that promises to take your taste buds on a journey of pure indulgence and luxury. Every bite is a sensory experience, featuring premium [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>We pride ourselves on following traditional Italian cuisine; whilst adding our&nbsp;luxurious touch.</p>



<p>Elevate your dining experience with our latest addition to the menu &#8211; the Golden Truffle Pizza. It&#8217;s an Italian masterpiece that promises to take your taste buds on a journey of pure indulgence and luxury. Every bite is a sensory experience, featuring premium ingredients and heavenly flavors that will leave you wanting more.</p>



<p>This true culinary delight is now available at both of our branches, West Walk and Al Hazm, where you can immerse yourself in a world of opulence and sophistication. Don&#8217;t settle for less when you can have the best. Treat yourself to the ultimate dining experience and indulge in the Golden Truffle Pizza today!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Branch Opening &#8211; West Walk</title>
		<link>./../../../new-branch-opening-west-walk/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Antonie Cruz]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 13:57:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Pasta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[al waab]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[branch]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doha]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hazm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[italian]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[new]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[opening]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[qatar]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[restaurant]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sasso]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[west walk]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1217</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We are thrilled to announce that the doors to our highly anticipated new branch at West Walk are finally open, and we cordially invite you to join us on a culinary journey of exquisite Italian fine dining. As soon as you step inside our new location, you will be transported to a world of luxury [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>We are thrilled to announce that the doors to our highly anticipated new branch at West Walk are finally open, and we cordially invite you to join us on a culinary journey of exquisite Italian fine dining.</p>



<p>As soon as you step inside our new location, you will be transported to a world of luxury and indulgence, where attention to detail is paramount, and every aspect of your dining experience has been meticulously curated to ensure your absolute satisfaction.</p>



<p>From the elegant and sophisticated decor to the impeccable service provided by our knowledgeable and attentive staff, every element has been thoughtfully considered to create an unforgettable dining experience.</p>



<p>Our menu is a celebration of the finest and freshest ingredients, skillfully crafted by our expert chefs to deliver a symphony of flavors and textures that will tantalize your taste buds and leave you craving more.</p>



<p>Whether you&#8217;re celebrating a special occasion, enjoying a romantic evening, or simply looking for an unforgettable dining experience, our new branch at West Walk promises to take Italian fine dining to a whole new level.</p>



<p>So come and join us, and experience the very best in Italian cuisine, served with elegance, style, and a touch of luxury. We can&#8217;t wait to welcome you through our doors and make your dining dreams a reality.</p>



<p><strong>.</strong></p>



<p><strong>Location: <a href="https://bit.ly/SassoMaps">7F2C+536 West Walk, Al Sidr St, Doha</a></strong></p>



<div class="mapouter"><div class="gmap_canvas"><iframe width="100%" height="500" id="gmap_canvas" src="https://maps.google.com/maps?q=7F2C+456%20West%20Walk,%20Al%20Sidr%20St,%20Doha&amp;t=&amp;z=19&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;iwloc=&amp;output=embed" frameborder="0" scrolling="no" marginheight="0" marginwidth="0"></iframe><a href="https://embedgooglemap.net/124/"></a><br><style>.mapouter{position:relative;text-align:right;height:500px;width:100%;}</style><a href="https://www.embedgooglemap.net/"></a><style>.gmap_canvas {overflow:hidden;background:none!important;height:500px;width:100%;}</style></div></div>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Favourite Italian Fine Dining Restaurant in Doha 2022</title>
		<link>./../../../favourite-italian-fine-dining-restaurant-in-doha-2022/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sasso]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 10:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Awards]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[2022]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[doha]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[FACT magazine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[favourite]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[gcc]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hazm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[italian fine dining]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sasso]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1178</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Annual FACT Dining Awards celebrates the best of GCC’s culinary scene. FACT Magazine has become the dining authority in Doha, celebrating the leaders of the industry. All winners were awarded based on both public votes and critique opinions and received their accolades amongst their peers. There were two awards in key categories;&#160;Favourite&#160;awards were decided [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Annual FACT Dining Awards celebrates the best of GCC’s culinary scene. FACT Magazine has become the dining authority in Doha, celebrating the leaders of the industry.</p>



<p>All winners were awarded based on both public votes and critique opinions and received their accolades amongst their peers. There were two awards in key categories;&nbsp;<em>Favourite</em>&nbsp;awards were decided by the public through an online voting system, whereas the&nbsp;<em>Best&nbsp;</em>awards were decided by FACT’s editorial panel.</p>



<p>We are proud to announce, Sasso has been awarded the most&nbsp;<em>Favourite Italian Fine Dining Restaurant in Doha</em>&nbsp;<em>2022</em>&nbsp;by the FACT Magazine Doha. We promise to continue raising the standards for authentic gourmet food served to you with passion.</p>



<p>We would like to thank everyone for your support! We would also like to thank our team for their incredible effort.&nbsp;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spicy Rigatoni Burrata</title>
		<link>./../../../spicy-rigatoni-buratta/index.html</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[sasso]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 14:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Pasta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[buratta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hazm]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pasta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[rigatoni]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sasso]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[spicy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">./../../../index.html?p=1138</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We pride ourselves on following traditional Italian cuisine; whilst adding our&#160;flare&#160;take. A pasta dish is only as good as its ingredients. That’s why we import our spices and use top-quality ingredients in each of our dishes, especially our newly created Spicy Rigatoni Burrata – A New &#38; Exclusive Doha’s Favourite Dish. Sasso presents the exclusive [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>We pride ourselves on following traditional Italian cuisine; whilst adding our&nbsp;flare&nbsp;take.</p>



<p>A pasta dish is only as good as its ingredients. That’s why we import our spices and use top-quality ingredients in each of our dishes, especially our newly created Spicy Rigatoni Burrata – A New &amp; Exclusive Doha’s Favourite Dish.</p>



<p>Sasso presents the exclusive dish in Doha; The Spicy Rigatoni Burrata &#8211; a spicy twist on a classic pasta dish with fresh onions and garlic, slathered in a rich pink sauce, and topped with premium quality creamy burrata flown directly from Italy to perfectly balance out the kick –&nbsp;ideal for a meatless meal!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
